<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Pages on Dermalyze</title>
        <link>https://dermalyze.tech/page/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Pages on Dermalyze</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Dermalyze</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dermalyze.tech/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>About Us</title>
        <link>https://dermalyze.tech/about-us/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dermalyze.tech/about-us/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;inspiration&#34;&gt;Inspiration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;        AI and machine learning models have tremendously grown in usage due to their advancements in computing power. More and more, the open-source AI community continues to grow and these advanced models are reaching even the hands of hobbyists. Our inspiration for this project comes from the growth of this new technology; we want to create our own model that will detect and identify skin conditions and recommend treatments based off of that. This project also serves as a great learning experience of the both of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-it-does&#34;&gt;What it does&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;        Our model takes a picture of skin and sends that to a machine learning model, which analyzes it for any skin conditions. We feed our model with a bunch of images from a database containing images of certain skin conditions. These labeled images help train the model on what to look for, and when it notices a pattern from what it has seen in training images on a brand new image, then it recognizes which skin condition it could be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next-for-dermalyze&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s next for Dermalyze&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;        We would like to continue developing our model by making the training and pre-processing steps more optimal. We intend to keep this app as accessible as possible because we found that many of the AIs out there are locked behind a paywall. By keeping our app free, we can increase awareness about existing solutions. To maintain our project&amp;rsquo;s sustainability, we can look into using affiliate links, such as Amazon, to provide users with links to buy products instead of just stating them, allowing us to pocket some money to invest in keeping a server online.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>https://dermalyze.tech/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dermalyze.tech/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Links</title>
        <link>https://dermalyze.tech/links/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dermalyze.tech/links/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here you can find all the links related to our project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--To use this feature, add `links` section to frontmatter.

This page&#39;s frontmatter:

```yaml
links:
  - title: GitHub
    description: GitHub is the world&#39;s largest software development platform.
    website: https://github.com
    image: https://github.githubassets.com/images/modules/logos_page/GitHub-Mark.png
  - title: TypeScript
    description: TypeScript is a typed superset of JavaScript that compiles to plain JavaScript.
    website: https://www.typescriptlang.org
    image: ts-logo-128.jpg
```

`image` field accepts both local and external images.--&gt;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>https://dermalyze.tech/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://dermalyze.tech/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
